如果我定义...这里有三个储蓄帐户，
我用不同的余额进行了初始化。
假设我想把三个帐户组成数组，
对这个数组调用sort，会发生什么？
由于余额都是数字，我们知道如何比较，
所以这个就可行吗？如果不可行，那是不是
我添加一个比较方法或向sort传递比较方法
就可行了吗？是不是认为不可行，
但如果为储蓄帐户定义一个宇宙飞船操作符就可行了？
还是说，这个就是不可行，因为这不是basic，
太麻烦了，而且没有内置方式与操作符进行比较。
第一轮投票。问题还没读完我就已经看到有人举牌了。
大多数选红色的。
你们今天不得了啊。现在把答案过一遍。
" It
“是可行的，因为可以比较帐户余额。”
works because the account balances get compared." Well, that's
我们当然希望是这样的情况，但帐户比较
certainly what we would like to be the case, but comparing
不同于整数型比较，所以不对。
accounts isn't the same as comparing integers, so that's not it.
如果向sort传递一个比较方法，那不是Ruby的方式，
If we pass a comparison method to sort, that's not the Ruby way,
对吧？在Ruby里面，sort会对你想要排序的内容进行假定，
right? The Ruby way is sort makes some assumptions about the
尤其是它知道如何与排序对象的实例进行比较。
thing you're trying to sort, in particular that the thing knows
正确答案是：
how to compare itself to other instances of that thing. The
如果我们为储蓄帐户定义宇宙飞船操作符，
correct answer is: If we define the spaceship operator for
对了，如何定义呢？
savings accounts ... and by the way, how would we define it? An
简单的做法是，就和这个例子一样：
easy way would just be to say, as in this example: Here's a way
这是对银行帐户定义比较的办法。就是这样，结果出来了。
to define comparisons on bank accounts. Here it is. It's coming
还有两分钟。这就是对银行帐户定义比较的方式。
now. We have two minutes left, yes. Here's the way you define
我很懒，所以我只定义宇宙飞船，然后把
comparison on bank accounts. I'm lazy, so I'm just going to
[comp- pra- bowl 00:01:40]包含起来，
define spaceship and then I'm going to include [ comp- pra- bowl
免费得到其它的东西。如果你不相信，
00:01:40] to get the other ones for free. In case you don't
我会把代码拷贝和粘贴过来。
believe me, I will copy and paste that code. I already had the
我已经定义了类帐户，那么现在...记不记得
class account defined, so now ... remember I had these accounts
这些帐户余额是很高的？可以说...OK？发言人2：[ Inaudible 00:02:03]
with high balances? I can say ... okay? Speaker 2:	[ Inaudible
发言人1：千真万确。（大笑）
00:02:03]. Speaker 1: True in so many ways. ( Laughing) What's
这里传达的意思是什么？Ruby提供了很多有用的功能来
the message here? Ruby provides a lot of useful functionality to
做你想做的事。你的任务...已经变化...
already do the work you need to do. Your job ... it's already
你应该以最少的劳动
varies in ... you need to do the least amount of new work
获取需要的功能。
possible to get the functionality you need. When you have
如果你想重复使用某些行为，可以把它们放进模块里。
behaviors you want to reuse, you can put them into a module.
只要你表达清楚模块在它融入的类里会遇到什么，
That module can be mixed into many classes as long as you make
那个模块可以融入很多类。
clear what does the module expect from the classes that you're
如果你要重复使用implementation（实现），
mixing it into. If you want to reuse implementation, then you'd
那应该用传统的办法。类是有祖先的，
use the traditional thing. Classes have ancestors, they have
也有子类。和你们学JAVA的人想的相反，
sub- classes. As we'll see, contrary to what you might think
大多数时候你们想要的是第一种。
coming from the JAVA world, remarkably often, what you want is
你们不想重复使用implementation（实现），
the first one. You don't want to reuse implementation; you want
而是想定义行为并重复使用它们。
to define behaviors and reuse them.